You know what's cheaper than Grok 4.6?
Paying nothing at all.
Exactly. Free model on OpenRouter, man.
Okay, let's go.
Yeah.
Get Grok, get OpenAI.
We have something better.
Exactly. All of that is garbage. Put that on the side because it's too expensive.
I refuse to pay for my AI now.
Yes. And it's not only for good developer sales, for everybody.
Yeah.
Last week, OpenRouter announced 0xalpha was in stealth mode, aka like they launch a model
and they are going to get your prompt and see if you like it and then launch it a week after.
So yeah, now that we know that 0xalpha is z.ai 5.3 flash and during a full week, everyone was
trying to guess based on the input, the output of the model, et cetera, like which model it was.
It's basically lasted like 15 minutes.
Everyone was already talking about GLM 5.3 just after the launch.
And for a week, like 42 trillion tokens in six days, yeah, open code.
Did you try it or not?
I didn't try it.
Yeah.
It could have been like a billion more.
I didn't find any crazy, big mistake stuff because even like the benchmark was like,
in some benchmark, it was on pair with Fable 5.
And for free.
And we had that for free for a week, but I had some issues.
Try testing the model while in open code.
Sometimes it just like stopped working.
I was not able to see the results in the station.
It just like a build, build, build, stop building.
What's happening?
I was building, build, build, build and stop again.
Yeah.
On the free one, so many people are using it.
Probably spikes in the usage and then it just goes out of a connection or something.
Yeah.
Because of that stealth morph, I decided like to retry open code.
And even on cursor, you can do that on cursor by changing the API keys.
So you can bring your open router key to cursor to use the cursor interface to use free models.
And I haven't like retry open code because it was a CLI and it was like
working the best with like this stealth model.
And yeah, now I've discovered even more free models because I like to pay.
But yeah, if you can get those free models for free, that's even better.
You can just use free AI now.
Yeah.
Well, you need cursor, but you don't need a subscription to change it.
Or do you put in your own API?
I don't think so because it's using your...
Okay.
So it's using the API and you just get the software.
So that's it.
Yes.
So you have a nice UI to use AI basically.
What can we build with those little free models?
I want to try them.
I want to try them now by building a YouTube transcript.
So we drop a link, we give a link, we get the transcript and if it will build that correctly,
then I want to have the clip.
So it will cut the clip of the best moment that we have doing a live stream.
Okay.
So basically at the end of this video, we can drop the URL in and it will create all the clips for us.
That's what I hope it will build with a free model.
With a free model.
And in 30 minutes.
Yes, exactly.
Let's go.
Okay, nice.
So I have Muse on the left and 0xalpha on the right.
And I want to use the prompt.
So we are building a small standalone TypeScript tool called YouTube Distiller.
Pass the YouTube link and you get back what the video actually said.
Just a handful of moments worth watching.
Cut and playable.
Yeah, read only.
Do not write code yet.
It has two faces of one engine.
It runs the full step below and emits progress even when it goes.
CLI, server.
The UI is a simple static HTML5.
No React, no Bundler, whatever.
Pipeline.
YouTube downloads.
Download the video and the English auto-caption in GZone 3.
Pass the GZone 3.
One request to open router.
Free route with the entire transcript.
Build in five minutes and to escape as requested.
Stay.
Yeah, I see like the time estimation.
It's pure garbage.
It's crazy.
It's the same thing if you put in and you say create a plan for this and now give me
the estimate in time and in costs.
I think it still does every estimate and the same time that people do it without AI.
Yeah, no one percent.
Because the data set is time estimation based on AI on human Reddit posts, right?
So yeah.
YouTube Distiller.
Pass the YouTube link.
Brief.
Three, five ranked moments.
Cut in playable.
One model request per video.
Left to the estimation.
Download start.
Okay, let's go.
Request format is not available.
Use list format.
What?
Fetching video.
How are you capturing the caption if there is no video?
I'm gonna drop that.
Download done.
Working.
You.
Are you doing anything?
It did find it.
Is it fake?
Fetch video.
Parsing.
Okay.
Analyzing transcript.
One request.
Okay.
I'm gonna.
Cutting five people.
Wait.
Okay.
Yes, it does.
Here it is.
A livestream demo of Grog, Grogbot.
End to end lead gen demo with King.
Yeah, King was my bot.
Yeah.
Okay, wait.
I'm gonna cut that.
Took the segment.
Smart.
Okay, that's sick.
Because like, see this, that's effect.
That's what I use for the, for the transition in the video from one chapter to another, right?
Walk through the food pipeline.
Google search from end of end leads.
Prom generation.
Email draft.
Lateral agent.
Org shots.
Yeah.
One minute.
Bro, that's, that could be clips for Twitter.
Yeah, but people are trying to do this with Claude.
And they are working for an hour to copy, paste, put the URL in, ask it.
You can just better code your own solution.
That's so much faster.
And it's working.
And it's free.
Yeah.
This is cool.
Like, bro, that, that, that costs zero.
And it gave results.
Like, some prompt you find a lead that you just need to find 1000.
I'll do this automatically.
Then it will example.
Yeah.
And I think you can imagine how I need.
Okay.
Why is it refreshing all the time?
What's still working?
Yeah.
But every time it creates a video, it refreshes.
Not fake real bug, no fixed.
You eat.
Oh my God.
That's I love AI bro.
And again, we don't need an employee to do this for us.
Make sure you test the different models that are available because you see,
even if people say that is the best model.
Yeah.
Now you have to prove the other one is working.
I mean, yeah.
Like it's crazy.
I mean, you don't have those gaps with like the frontier model from entropy can have.
Yeah.
February five is still the best model though.
Also the most expensive.
Yeah.
I mean, I will, I think I will try to have those.
I will just one prompt the same distiller stuff with codex and cloud the amount of entropy.
So it would be 5.6.
So, but yeah, it could be interesting to, to try that.
But yeah.
Okay.
Whatever.
So yeah, like we can even walk with free models now.
Yes, it works.
And it showed and it makes good solutions.
You see, we had like five videos instantly.
That's nuts.
Like I didn't expect that to be that fast with not the model I wanted to test first.
But the secret sauce is tell it we need it in five minutes because we're on live stream
and it will just do everything in five minutes.
True.
Oh yeah.
Through that.
Yeah.
The shortcut is like, bro, you have 30 minutes, 30 seconds because if you don't,
I'm going to cut your electricity off.
Yeah, yeah.
The whole world is going through damnation.
Just do it in 30 seconds.
Yeah.
So yeah, for everyone who was prompting right now, tell your Claude that his bandwidth is
going to be reduced.
Yes.
Yeah.
Michel, thank you so much for your time.
Thank you for the demo.
That was fun.
And yeah, like next week, someplace.
Oh yeah, no.
Yeah.
Someplace, sometime.
Same on mine.
Yeah.
Cheers, man.
Thank you.
Bye.
Yeah.
Like, subscribe, share.
Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, whatever.